curvesinformation.com 2018-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Curves.com

Effective Date: March 28, 2016

The privacy policies described below are a promise made to our online visitors by Curves International, Inc. and their subsidiaries (“Curves”).This privacy policy describes how Curves collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site [www.curves.com](http://www.curves.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?**

We respect the privacy of our online visitors. We may collect information on or through this site that can personally identify you. For example, we collect personally identifiable information which you volunteer to us to respond to visitor questions and comments about us and our products and services, and to mail e-newsletters. We may also collect your first and last name, email address and postal code when you join any of our programs or request a consultation. In addition, we may also collect demographic and other data for market research, advertising and promotional purposes, we may collect your site usage data through our use of Internet cookie technology or similar devices, or we may receive information about you from our third parties franchisees in order to provide online membership services, under a requirement that your information is then subject to the terms of this policy while in our possession or control. Collectively, we call all of this information your Personal Data.

We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](mailto:curves@curves.com) (or if located in the European Union click here (<http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>)) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.At this time due to technical limitations we do not respond to browser do not track signals.

We may use your Personal Data to provide any services you have requested from us. We may also use your Personal Data to notify you about updates to our Web site, contact you with special offers of interest, or to and customize your Web site experience. If you do not want to receive marketing communications or e-newsletters from us, please email us at [membercomments@curves.com](mailto:membercomments@curves.com), call us at (800) 848-1096, or write to us at: Customer Service, Curves International, 100 Ritchie Road, Woodway, TX 76712, or go to <http://mkto.curves.com/Email_Preferences.html> and update your preferences.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [membercomments@curves.com](mailto:membercomments@curves.com).

Our site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us at [membercomments@curves.com](mailto:membercomments@curves.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**How We Protect Your Personal Data**

The security of your personal data is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards, such as secure socket layers (SSL), 128 bit encryption, to protect sensitive personal data, such as credit card number, submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is one hundred percent secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [membercomments@curves.com](mailto:membercomments@curves.com).

**How to Access and/or Correct Your Personal Data**

If your Personal Data changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend or delete it by emailing us at [membercomments@curves.com](mailto:membercomments@curves.com), by contacting us by telephone or postal mail as listed below, or by contacting your local Curves Club. We will respond to a request to access Personal Data within 30 days.

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Disclosures Required By Law or Business Transaction**

We may from time to time need to disclose certain information, which may include your Personal Data, to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, search warrant, in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a law enforcement agency request. Also, if there is a change of control in one of our businesses (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), or a sale or transfer of its assets, customer information, which may include your Personal Data, could be disclosed to a potential purchaser under an agreement to maintain confidentiality, or could be sold or transferred as part of that transaction, in such case, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal data.

**What Are Cookies and How Do We Use Them?**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to maintain a log in session. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies to save user preferences. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as logging in, contests, surveys or shopping cart will be impacted.

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Curves,itsaffiliates,marketing partners, analytics or service providers. We use these technologies, which do not identify individual users,to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Third Party Service Providers**

We will use reasonable means to protect the confidentiality of your Personal Data while in our possession or control. We will not knowingly share, sell or rent any of your Personal Data with any third party other than as described in this privacy policy. We will share your Personal Data with our service providers who assist us in providing the information and/or services we are providing to you. To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we would only do so if that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this privacy policy and only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Any non-personally identifiable information, communications and material you send to this site or to us by e-mail, or which we obtain from third parties without promises of confidentiality, may be kept, used and disclosed by us on a non-confidential basis. We are free to use and reproduce any such information freely, and for any purpose whatsoever. Specifically, we will be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose, including developing, manufacturing or marketing products. You agree that any information you send to this site must be truthful, not violate the rights of others and be legal for us to possess and use.

**Links to Third-Party Sites**

Our site includes links to third-party web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Curves. If you submit personal data to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any site you visit.

**Personal Data of Minors**

Our site is not targeted to persons under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect any Personal Data from children under the age of 13.

**Changes to This Policy**

We may modify this policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on this site. Unless we specifically provide otherwise, this policy only applies to this site and our online activities, and does not apply to any of our offline activities. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this web site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Your Consent**

By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy. If we materially change our privacy policies and procedures, we will notify you by e-mail or post a notice of the changes on this site as described above.

Curves Legal, Curves International, 100 Ritchie Road, Woodway, TX 76712.
